const quizData = [
  /* Grammer Questions */
  {
    "Quiz":"Grammar",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is a noun?",
    "answer":"A person, place, thing, or idea",
    "option": [
      "A person, place, thing, or idea",
      "A type of verb",
      "A punctuation mark",
      "A unit of measurement"
      ]
      
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "What is an adjective?",
    "answer": "A word that describes or modifies a noun",
    "option": [
      "A type of verb",
      "A person, place, thing, or idea",
      "A word that describes or modifies a noun",
      "A form of punctuation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "What is the superlative form of 'big'?",
    "answer": "Biggest",
    "option": [
      "Bigly",
      "Bigger",
      "Biggest",
      "Bigged"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "Which of the following is an interjection?",
    "answer": "Wow!",
    "option": [
      "Wow!",
      "Running",
      "Quickly",
      "Table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "What is a pronoun?",
    "answer": "A word that takes the place of a noun",
    "option": [
      "A person, place, thing, or idea",
      "A type of verb",
      "A word that takes the place of a noun",
      "A form of punctuation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "Identify the preposition in the sentence: 'The cat is under the table.'",
    "answer": "Under",
    "option": [
      "Cat",
      "Is",
      "Under",
      "Table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "What is the plural form of 'child'?",
    "answer": "Children",
    "option": [
      "Childs",
      "Childrens",
      "Child",
      "Children"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "In which tense is the sentence 'She will sing at the concert.'?",
    "answer": "Future",
    "option": [
      "Past",
      "Present",
      "Future",
      "Progressive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 9,
    "question": "Which of the following is a compound sentence?",
    "answer": "He studied hard, yet he failed the exam.",
    "option": [
      "He studied hard.",
      "He failed the exam.",
      "He studied hard, yet he failed the exam.",
      "He quickly finished his lunch."
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Grammar",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "What is the infinitive form of the verb 'to run'?",
    "answer": "Run",
    "option": [
      "Running",
      "Runs",
      "Run",
      "Ran"
    ]
  },
/* Vocab Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is the meaning of 'perceive'?",
    "answer": "To become aware or conscious of something",
    "option": [
      "To ignore",
      "To become aware or conscious of something",
      "To create",
      "To finish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "Define 'obsolete'.",
    "answer": "No longer in use; outdated",
    "option": [
      "Modern",
      "Brand new",
      "No longer in use; outdated",
      "Functional"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Provide a synonym for 'enthusiastic'.",
    "answer": "Eager, passionate",
    "option": [
      "Eager, passionate",
      "Lazy",
      "Tired",
      "Bored"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "What is the meaning of 'contribute'?",
    "answer": "To give or add to something",
    "option": [
      "To divide",
      "To subtract",
      "To give or add to something",
      "To isolate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "What does 'anticipate' mean?",
    "answer": "To expect or foresee",
    "option": [
      "To forget",
      "To expect or foresee",
      "To ignore",
      "To invent"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "Define 'persistent'.",
    "answer": "Continuing firmly or obstinately in a course of action",
    "option": [
      "Continuing firmly or obstinately in a course of action",
      "Weak",
      "Changing",
      "Random"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "What does 'analyze' mean?",
    "answer": "To examine in detail",
    "option": [
      "To ignore",
      "To examine in detail",
      "To create",
      "To finish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "Provide a synonym for 'resilient'.",
    "answer": "Capable of recovering quickly from difficulties",
    "option": [
      "Fragile",
      "Stagnant",
      "Old",
      "Capable of recovering quickly from difficulties",
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 9,
    "question": "Define 'cooperate'.",
    "answer": "To work together towards a common goal",
    "option": [
      "To compete",
      "To work together towards a common goal",
      "To argue",
      "To fight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Vocabulary",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "What is the meaning of 'evaluate'?",
    "answer": "To assess or judge the value or importance of something",
    "option": [
      "To ignore",
      "To create",
      "To assess or judge the value or importance of something",
      "To finish"
    ]
  },
  /* Spelling bEE Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'etateleiv' to form a word.",
    "answer": "levitate",
    "option": [
      "evetilate",
      "televatie",
      "eliteavet",
      "levitate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'garmmea' to form a word.",
    "answer": "grammar",
    "option": [
      "grammar",
      "garagem",
      "gammare",
      "grammare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'inofnartmio' to form a word.",
    "answer": "information",
    "option": [
      "formation",
      "information",
      "firmation",
      "informtion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'voicder' to form a word.",
    "answer": "discovery",
    "option": [
      "covdriey",
      "discovery",
      "derycivo",
      "cdivoyer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'cericnfoe' to form a word.",
    "answer": "conference",
    "option": [
      "confierenc",
      "confercien",
      "conference",
      "confrencie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'etqursoi' to form a word.",
    "answer": "question",
    "option": [
      "requestio",
      "inquires",
      "questions",
      "question"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'steionclia' to form a word.",
    "answer": "elocinatis",
    "option": [
      "instelicao",
      "socialtien",
      "elocinatis",
      "instaicleo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'eptarilv' to form a word.",
    "answer": "prevital",
    "option": [
      "parvitle",
      "private",
      "prevital",
      "viraplet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 9,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'oncintsiet' to form a word.",
    "answer": "conscient",
    "option": [
      "coetnnisti",
      "conscient",
      "connistiet",
      "scientonic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'crbiliaity' to form a word.",
    "answer": "calibirty",
    "option": [
      "briliacty",
      "cralibity",
      "calibirty",
      "clarity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Spelling Bee",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "Unscramble the letters 'crbiliaity' to form a word.",
    "answer": "calibirty",
    "option": [
      "briliacty",
      "cralibity",
      "calibirty",
      "clarity"
    ]
  },
  /* Addition Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is 789 + 432?",
    "answer": "1221",
    "option": [
      "1211",
      "1112",
      "1221",
      "1122"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "What is 9876 + 5432?",
    "answer": "15308",
    "option": [
      "15432",
      "15308",
      "15280",
      "15520"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "What is 12345 + 67890?",
    "answer": "80235",
    "option": [
      "80135",
      "80025",
      "80235",
      "80325"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "What is 876543 + 210987?",
    "answer": "1087530",
    "option": [
      "1085760",
      "1087530",
      "1083705",
      "1095307"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "What is 123456 + 654321?",
    "answer": "777777",
    "option": [
      "777777",
      "777888",
      "766666",
      "788888"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "What is 987654 + 123456?",
    "answer": "1111110",
    "option": [
      "1111110",
      "1122220",
      "1100011",
      "1111101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "What is 543210 + 876543?",
    "answer": "1419753",
    "option": [
      "1417953",
      "1409753",
      "1419753",
      "1417359"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "What is 9876543 + 1234567?",
    "answer": "11111110",
    "option": [
      "11111011",
      "11111000",
      "11111110",
      "11111001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 9,
    "question": "What is 13579 + 24680?",
    "answer": "38259",
    "option": [
      "38259",
      "38269",
      "39259",
      "38258"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Addition",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "What is 24680 + 13579?",
    "answer": "38259",
    "option": [
      "38269",
      "38259",
      "39259",
      "38258"
    ]
  },
/* Subtraction Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is 789 - 432?",
    "answer": "357",
    "option": [
      "357",
      "345",
      "447",
      "322"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "What is 9876 - 5432?",
    "answer": "4444",
    "option": [
      "4321",
      "4444",
      "5344",
      "5566"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "What is 12345 - 6789?",
    "answer": "5556",
    "option": [
      "5556",
      "5467",
      "5656",
      "5678"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "What is 876543 - 210987?",
    "answer": "665556",
    "option": [
      "655556",
      "676556",
      "665556",
      "654556"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "What is 123456 - 65432?",
    "answer": "58024",
    "option": [
      "57024",
      "59024",
      "58024",
      "56024"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "What is 987654 - 123456?",
    "answer": "864198",
    "option": [
      "875198",
      "864198",
      "853198",
      "875298"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "What is 543210 - 87654?",
    "answer": "455556",
    "option": [
      "455556",
      "465556",
      "445556",
      "465656"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "What is 9876543 - 1234567?",
    "answer": "8641976",
    "option": [
      "8642976",
      "8641976",
      "8741976",
      "8741876"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 9,
    "question": "What is 13579 - 2468?",
    "answer": "11111",
    "option": [
      "11211",
      "11011",
      "11111",
      "11311"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Subtraction",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "What is 24680 - 13579?",
    "answer": "11101",
    "option": [
      "11201",
      "11301",
      "11101",
      "11001"
    ]
  },
/* Multiplication Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is 7 x 9?",
    "answer": "63",
    "option": [
      "54",
      "63",
      "72",
      "81"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "What is 12 x 8?",
    "answer": "96",
    "option": [
      "88",
      "96",
      "104",
      "112"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "What is 15 x 6?",
    "answer": "90",
    "option": [
      "84",
      "96",
      "102",
      "90"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "What is 9 x 11?",
    "answer": "99",
    "option": [
      "99",
      "88",
      "110",
      "121"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "What is 16 x 7?",
    "answer": "112",
    "option": [
      "105",
      "112",
      "119",
      "126"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "What is 14 x 5?",
    "answer": "70",
    "option": [
      "65",
      "75",
      "70",
      "80"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "What is 11 x 10?",
    "answer": "110",
    "option": [
      "99",
      "105",
      "110",
      "121"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "What is 13 x 9?",
    "answer": "117",
    "option": [
      "104",
      "117",
      "130",
      "143"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 9,
    "question": "What is 18 x 4?",
    "answer": "72",
    "option": [
      "72",
      "64",
      "80",
      "88"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Multiplication",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "What is 20 x 3?",
    "answer": "60",
    "option": [
      "55",
      "65",
      "70",
      "60"
    ]
  },
  /* Living Things Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is the process by which living organisms produce energy from food?",
    "answer": "Respiration",
    "option": [
      "Photosynthesis",
      "Digestion",
      "Respiration",
      "Metabolism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "What is the process by which green plants use sunlight to synthesize food from carbon dioxide and water?",
    "answer": "photosynthesis",
    "option": [
      "respiration",
      "digestion",
      "photosynthesis",
      "metabolism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Which organelle is known as the 'powerhouse' of the cell because it produces energy?",
    "answer": "mitochondria",
    "option": [
      "nucleus",
      "chloroplast",
      "mitochondria",
      "ribosome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "What is the basic structural and functional unit of all living organisms?",
    "answer": "cell",
    "option": [
      "tissue",
      "organ",
      "cell",
      "organism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "What is the green pigment found in plants that is essential for photosynthesis?",
    "answer": "chlorophyll",
    "option": [
      "melanin",
      "hemoglobin",
      "chlorophyll",
      "carotene"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "What is the process by which organisms break down organic matter and convert it into energy?",
    "answer": "metabolism",
    "option": [
      "respiration",
      "digestion",
      "photosynthesis",
      "metabolism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "Which kingdom of living organisms includes multicellular organisms that lack cell walls, can move voluntarily, and usually ingest food?",
    "answer": "Animalia",
    "option": [
      "Plantae",
      "Animalia",
      "Fungi",
      "Protista"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "Which domain of living organisms includes all prokaryotic organisms?",
    "answer": "Bacteria",
    "option": [
      "Bacteria",
      "Archaea",
      "Eukarya",
      "Protozoa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 9,
    "question": "What is the process by which living organisms take in oxygen and release carbon dioxide?",
    "answer": "respiration",
    "option": [
      "photosynthesis",
      "digestion",
      "respiration",
      "metabolism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Living Things",
    "number": 10,
    "question": "What is the process by which living organisms break down food into simpler substances for energy?",
    "answer": "digestion",
    "option": [
      "photosynthesis",
      "respiration",
      "digestion",
      "metabolism"
    ]
  },
/* Plants Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is the process by which plants lose water vapor through small openings in their leaves?",
    "answer": "transpiration",
    "option": [
      "photosynthesis",
      "respiration",
      "transpiration",
      "pollination"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "What is the tissue in plants responsible for transporting water and minerals from the roots to the rest of the plant?",
    "answer": "xylem",
    "option": [
      "phloem",
      "xylem",
      "epidermis",
      "mesophyll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Which gas is absorbed by plants during photosynthesis and released during respiration?",
    "answer": "carbon dioxide",
    "option": [
      "oxygen",
      "carbon dioxide",
      "nitrogen",
      "water vapor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "Which part of the plant anchors it to the soil and absorbs water and minerals?",
    "answer": "root",
    "option": [
      "stem",
      "leaf",
      "root",
      "flower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "What is the male reproductive organ of a flower called?",
    "answer": "stamen",
    "option": [
      "pistil",
      "stigma",
      "stamen",
      "petal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "Which process involves the transfer of pollen grains from the anther to the stigma of a flower?",
    "answer": "pollination",
    "option": [
      "fertilization",
      "germination",
      "pollination",
      "reproduction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "What is the process by which plants convert light energy into chemical energy to produce glucose?",
    "answer": "photosynthesis",
    "option": [
      "respiration",
      "transpiration",
      "photosynthesis",
      "pollination"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Plants",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "Which tissue in plants is responsible for transporting sugars produced during photosynthesis to various parts of the plant?",
    "answer": "phloem",
    "option": [
      "xylem",
      "phloem",
      "epidermis",
      "mesophyll"
    ]
  },
  /* Magnets Questions */
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 1,
    "question": "What is the property of a magnet that allows it to attract objects made of iron, nickel, or cobalt?",
    "answer": "magnetic force",
    "option": [
      "gravitational force",
      "magnetic force",
      "electric force",
      "frictional force"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 2,
    "question": "What is the region around a magnet where its magnetic force is felt?",
    "answer": "magnetic field",
    "option": [
      "magnetic region",
      "magnetic zone",
      "magnetic field",
      "magnetic space"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Which type of magnet retains its magnetism after being removed from a magnetic field?",
    "answer": "permanent magnet",
    "option": [
      "temporary magnet",
      "permanent magnet",
      "electromagnet",
      "ferromagnet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 4,
    "question": "What is the name of the material that is attracted to a magnet and can become magnetized itself?",
    "answer": "ferromagnetic material",
    "option": [
      "non-magnetic material",
      "magnetic material",
      "paramagnetic material",
      "ferromagnetic material"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 5,
    "question": "Which pole of a magnet points towards the Earth's geographic North Pole?",
    "answer": "north pole",
    "option": [
      "south pole",
      "north pole",
      "east pole",
      "west pole"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 6,
    "question": "What happens when opposite poles of two magnets are brought close together?",
    "answer": "they attract each other",
    "option": [
      "they attract each other",
      "they repel each other",
      "nothing happens",
      "they align with each other"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 7,
    "question": "What happens when like poles of two magnets are brought close together?",
    "answer": "they repel each other",
    "option": [
      "they attract each other",
      "they repel each other",
      "nothing happens",
      "they align with each other"
    ]
  },
  {
    "Quiz": "Magnets",
    "number": 8,
    "question": "Which type of magnet can be turned on and off by controlling the flow of electricity?",
    "answer": "electromagnet",
    "option": [
      "permanent magnet",
      "temporary magnet",
      "ferromagnet",
      "electromagnet"
    ]
  }
]



